<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home of Katheryn Fox on Comm-260 Spring 2023</title>
    <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home of Katheryn Fox on Comm-260 Spring 2023</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/about/</guid>
      <description>Final projects for Comm-260.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Share bikes in DC</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/bike-shares/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/bike-shares/</guid>
      <description>The Covid-19 outbreak in 2020 led to business shutting down, and people being socially isolated in their homes. This affected Bike Sharing services, as people were not leaving their homes as often. Capital Bikeshare, the official bikeshare programs for D.C., is steadily recovering from the fall in usage in 2020, following the Covid-19 outbreak.
Micro-mobility In 2022 the usage more than doubled from 2020, according to the data released by Capital Bikeshare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deaf Students Disproportionately More Likely to Experience Sexual Assault</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/gallaudet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/gallaudet/</guid>
      <description>A school for the deaf and hard of hearing, Gallaudet University’s average sexual assault rate was 12.6 cases per 1,000 students between 2014 and 2021.
Located in Washington D.C., Gallaudet University had nearly eight times as many instances of rape each year than the four largest neighboring colleges, according to the U.S. Department of Education’s Campus Safety and Security statistics. George Washington University, Georgetown University, American University, and Howard University each reported less than two cases per year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balling on a budget</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/ncaa_budgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/ncaa_budgets/</guid>
      <description>The NCAA March Madness basketball tournament is a place where anything can and will happen. What draws people in every year, however, are the underdogs, the Cinderella stories and the upsets.
The difference in talent between underdogs and higher seeded teams is enough to make most tournament upsets seem improbable, which is why fans love the March Madness tournament so much. It is a place where the improbable becomes reality. The NCAA website defines an upset as a lower seeded team beating a team at least two seeds above them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These kids have not been alright</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/mental_health/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/mental_health/</guid>
      <description>“I was in a hole,” said 20-year-old Emma Boothroyd in reflecting on their mental health throughout the COVID-19 pandemic. The college student is not alone in their suffering, as young adults remain among the most affected by mental illnesses in the United States.
In looking at clients under 30-years-old, individuals ages 18 to 20 were reported as the highest age group diagnosed with both depression and anxiety. This trend has remained consistent throughout the past six years as more individuals seek professional assistance for mental health related ailments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should Colleges Continue to Require SAT Scores?</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/standardized_testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/standardized_testing/</guid>
      <description>Students applying for college were forced to apply to schools that did not require SAT or ACT scores due to the cancellation of test taking facilities during the beginning of the pandemic in 2020.
American University sophomore, Michelle Wang, was one of these students. Wang says she had been preparing to take the SAT since her freshman year of high school. When the coronavirus spread throughout her homestate, California, she was faced with a dilemma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mass shootings in the U.S. are at a record high</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/mass_shootings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/mass_shootings/</guid>
      <description>Mass shootings are an American phenomenon. In 2023, the United States is setting a record pace for mass killings, with these horrific incidents happening roughly once a week.
Per the Gun Violence Archive, mass shootings are defined as incidents in which four or more victims are shot or killed, excluding the perpetrator, at the same location at roughly the same time. 208 mass shootings have happened in the U.S. this year with 21 alone in May.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contaminated drinking water </title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/drinking-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/drinking-water/</guid>
      <description>Many often assume that unsafe drinking water is an issue of the past, only felt today by countries in the global south. It’s easy to assume that safe drinking water is accessible in the United States, one of the wealthiest countries in the world.
Except, it’s not that simple for a quarter of Americans who do not have access to clean drinking water. For almost 90 million U.S. residents, this is an everyday problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The AU Women&#39;s Basketball Season</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/womens_basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/womens_basketball/</guid>
      <description>At American University in D.C., the men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s basketball season recently came to an end. Both ended up 7th in the league and made it to the Patriot League Championship. Yet the packed stands for the men&amp;rsquo;s games was a stark contrast to the fans that straggled in for the women.
The difference in attendance was reflected in the ticket prices. Demand was high enough for men that the box office could afford to set the tickets to 40$, while the women&amp;rsquo;s tickets stayed a constant 8$ a piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Food Chains Expand but at What Cost? </title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/fast_food/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/fast_food/</guid>
      <description>For Nairobi Toombs, a sophomore at Howard University, growing up in Chicago was a pivotal part of her upbringing. From bike rides with her father on the lakeshore to having attended the Whitney Young Magnet High School––the high school that Michelle Obama attended––Toombs said that she had more opportunities than her neighbors.
Toombs grew up on the South Shore almost her entire life, moving from a small condo near the lakeshore to a house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lung Cancer Rates Decline Rapidly As Americans Find Ways To Quit Smoking</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/smoking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/smoking/</guid>
      <description>In the 1930s and 1940s cigarette companies would advertise themselves as doctor-recommended. One R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company advertisement read “More doctors smoke Camels than any other cigarette.” In 1978 a law was passed that authorized school districts to equip high schools with designated smoking areas. After years of not only normalizing but encouraging tobacco use, Lung cancer is now the second most common cancer among both men and women trailing behind prostate cancer for men and breast cancer for women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Blurred Lines of Twitch Streams</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/twitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 09:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/twitch/</guid>
      <description>“As embarrassing as it is, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what he’s watching past video games.” said Christina Stino, a mother of two. Stino says her son spends most of his free time outside of school and extracurricular activities watching online gaming content. Stino, a single mother and owner of a hairdressing salon says she does not have the time she would like to monitor her childrens content consumption. “I got a charge on my credit card for Twitch and he said it was like Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Food and Obesity</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/obesity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/obesity/</guid>
      <description>When 21-year-old Chinese international student Shangman Zhao came to the United States to study, she found it difficult to strike a balance between her academic pursuits and maintaining a healthy diet. As a result, she started consuming more fast food, which led to weight gain.
&amp;ldquo;When I see the number on the scale, I really feel distressed,&amp;rdquo;&amp;quot; Zhao said.
Zhao&amp;rsquo;s experience is not uncommon, as global obesity rates have nearly doubled since 1975, with over 1 billion people worldwide classified as obese, including 650 million adults, 340 million adolescents, and 39 million children, according to the World Health Organization (WHO) .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verschwindende Deutsche</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/german_cleveland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/blog/german_cleveland/</guid>
      <description>Despite German immigrants being on the heftier end of Cleveland, Ohio&amp;rsquo;s population from the early 1800&amp;rsquo;s and onward, there ar very few representations of so many Clevelanders&amp;rsquo; heritage from Deutschland, as well as the decrease in German inhabitants of the city in recent years.
How do the numbers of German descendants in Cleveland today compare to that of the early settlement of the city? From 1870, there was a .9% decrease from the German population in Cleveland as recent as 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/blog/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/blog/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji-Unterstützung</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/de/blog/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/de/blog/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emojis können in einem Hugo-Projekt auf verschiedene Weise aktiviert werden.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Über mich</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/de/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/de/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo wurde in Go geschrieben und ist ein Open-Source-Generator für statische Sites, der unter der [Apache License 2.0.] (https://github.com/gohugoio/hugo/blob/master/LICENSE ) verfügbar ist. Hugo unterstützt TOML-, YAML- und JSON-Datendateitypen , Markdown- und HTML-Inhaltsdateien und verwendet Shortcodes, um Rich Content hinzuzufügen. Andere bemerkenswerte Funktionen sind Taxonomien, mehrsprachiger Modus, Bildverarbeitung, benutzerdefinierte Ausgabeformate, HTML/CSS/JS-Minifizierung und Unterstützung für Sass SCSS-Workflows.
Hugo nutzt eine Vielzahl von Open-Source-Projekten, darunter:
https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop https://github.com/spf13/cobra https://github.com/spf13/viper Hugo is ideal for blogs, corporate websites, creative portfolios, online magazines, single page applications or even a website with thousands of pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/de/blog/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/de/blog/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dieser Artikel bietet ein Beispiel für die grundlegende Markdown-Syntax, die in Hugo-Inhaltsdateien verwendet werden kann, und zeigt auch, ob grundlegende HTML-Elemente mit CSS in einem Hugo-Theme dekoriert sind.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/blog/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/blog/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Typesetting</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/blog/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/blog/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/blog/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/blog/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platzhaltertext</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/de/blog/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/de/blog/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reichhaltiger Inhalt</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/de/blog/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/de/blog/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo wird mit mehreren &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugos-built-in-shortcodes&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;
 für reichhaltige Inhalte geliefert, zusammen mit einer &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Privacy Config&lt;/a&gt;
 und einer Reihe einfacher Shortcodes, die statische und keine JS-Versionen verschiedener Social-Media-Einbettungen ermöglichen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rich Content</title>
      <link>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/blog/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://comm-260.github.io/spring-2023/en/blog/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo ships with several &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugos-built-in-shortcodes&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;
 for rich content, along with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Privacy Config&lt;/a&gt;
 and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
